Max Ravech: What's up, Matthew? How are you?
Max Ravech: I think you're on mute.
Matthew smith: Can you hear me?
Max Ravech: Yep, I got you.
Matthew smith: Okay, awesome. Sounds good, man. How was your weekend?
Max Ravech: Weekend was good, yeah, not too bad. How about yourself?
Matthew smith: It was chill, man, just got, caught up on a whole bunch of work, nothing too crazy.
Max Ravech: Nice. Where are you based?
Matthew smith: I'm in San Diego.
Max Ravech: San Diego. Alright, nice. Cool.
Matthew smith: How about you?
Max Ravech: I'm in New York, in the city.
Matthew smith: Okay, nice.
Matthew smith: Cool, yeah, I guess let's just hop into it, I don't want to take up too much of your time.
Max Ravech: Yeah.
Matthew smith: So, the agenda is to kind of just clarify and work through
Matthew smith: pretty much everything. We want to hash out all the… flush out the details. So, last week's call, we focused primarily on the exec side of BAMF, right? Banff Advisors… BAMP Advisors, excuse me.
Max Ravech: Yup.
Matthew smith: And so we prepared a document, just kind of going through all the workflows that we have so far.
Matthew smith: So, I'm gonna share that with you.
Matthew smith: Right now, and then…
Matthew smith: And we're gonna make sure these are good.
Matthew smith: And I apologize in advance if a lot of these are redundant or remedial questions. I know we've
Matthew smith: kind of discussed a lot of it, so… That's okay.
Max Ravech: Did you talk with Amanda yet?
Matthew smith: No, not yet. I have a call set for Tuesday, I believe.
Max Ravech: Okay.
Matthew smith: Yeah.
Matthew smith: And I think we're still waiting on a few… .
Max Ravech: Tech Logins, I saw that.
Matthew smith: Yes, exactly.
Matthew smith: How long been in New York?
Max Ravech: Four years?
Matthew smith: produce?
Max Ravech: Four years, yeah, I moved… I, I went to Pepperdine for undergrad.
Matthew smith: Nice.
Max Ravech: Malibu, and then I came back right after.
Matthew smith: Cool, how do you like it?
Max Ravech: New York I love it. It's a blast.
Matthew smith: expired.
Matthew smith: Yeah, good time, yeah.
Matthew smith: I still have not been, so…
Max Ravech: Ever?
Matthew smith: Weed. Yeah, yeah.
Max Ravech: Wow.
Max Ravech: I wouldn't come for the next few months. It gets crazy here.
Matthew smith: Yeah. For all.
Max Ravech: It's nuts. I would come, you know, May or October, it's gorgeous, but yeah, you should come.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Matthew smith: Solid. And then we…
Matthew smith: There you go.
Matthew smith: Nice.
Matthew smith: Share my screen here.
Matthew smith: Cool, then let me know if you can see it.
Max Ravech: Mmm… shown up.
Matthew smith: I'm sure.
Max Ravech: There you go.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Matthew smith: Alright, so here's the complete workflow mapping and automation roadmap. So we found that we can save 150 to 200 hours a month.
Matthew smith: Some of the key foundations that we found, there's a four-system data entry, right? So, for each client, you spend about 30 to 60 minutes per client.
Matthew smith: There's zero tracking for P2P introductions and training outcomes.
Matthew smith: 10 to 20 week… or 10 to 20 hours per week spent on extracting tasks from emails and notes.
Matthew smith: Human error and activity dashboards, reporting dashboards, and then fragmented data across, everything, which we already know.
Matthew smith: Cool, and so… We're gonna walk through this. We have…
Matthew smith: the inbound channels, right, so we have LinkedIn coming in.
Matthew smith: Email, referral, website, all dumps into Slack, the CRM, or HubSpot.
Matthew smith: The sales conversion, advisory driven, we have advisory members to follow up, there's no system for that. The notes are kept in Notion, no deal pipeline tracking, and no automated reminders.
Max Ravech: Yup.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Matthew smith: Contract generation, I believe that's you that handles that, right?
Max Ravech: TSQ does.
Matthew smith: TSQ, okay, TSQ. Yeah. TSQ…
Matthew smith: Sends out a contract, managing creates a DocuSign, client signs, and a TSQ emails team PDF confirmation.
Max Ravech: Yes.
Matthew smith: From there, we have the handoff, no lead tracking, lost opportunities, no follow-up automation, still dies from neglect, 24 to 48 hour contract delay, and then poor client experience.
Matthew smith: Equals matter coordination high friction.
Max Ravech: Definitely.
Matthew smith: Okay, everything following, everything's kind of exact, right?
Max Ravech: Yep. That's all, that's all right, yep.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Matthew smith: Step one is client ops receives contract PDF via email.
Matthew smith: And then step 2… Make sure all that's aligned.
Max Ravech: to…
Matthew smith: contract.
Matthew smith: Yeah.
Max Ravech: Sign advisors, like, yep, enter a contract, billing terms, mark unit at Tier 1 issues.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Max Ravech: Yeah, that's right.
Max Ravech: That's right, yup.
Max Ravech: We also have to, so, back up on that Notion one.
Max Ravech: So, a lot of the times, the sales calls, they do go into Notion, Automatically, just through Zoom.
Max Ravech: like, Zoom AI, or whatever you call it, it creates a Notion call…
Max Ravech: Thing. So we just have to go in, and after we create their client profile in Notion, we have to go and find those calls, and then tag them to their client page after the fact.
Max Ravech: So that's another thing we do.
Matthew smith: Okay, so create client profile in Notion, the Zoom comes in, drops it into Notion.
Matthew smith: And then… You have to update all of that manually, right?
Max Ravech: Yeah, we have to go and find the sales calls and tag them to the client.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Max Ravech: Because we don't make Notion profiles for people that aren't clients.
Matthew smith: Yeah, that makes sense, of course.
Matthew smith: Okay, one second.
Matthew smith: Yes.
Matthew smith: Anything else here?
Max Ravech: frickintender.
Max Ravech: Nope, that's alright.
Matthew smith: Amen.
Max Ravech: Which one is this? Oh, Contender. Yeah, yeah. That's alright.
Matthew smith: Google.
Max Ravech: Yeah, and those all, yeah, that's right. Those come from Notion, that Google Drive thing.
Matthew smith: Nice, nice.
Matthew smith: Okay, so these are the kickoff calls for your clients. Okay, so these… I just want to go through that.
Max Ravech: I knew a post offline transcripts.
Max Ravech: Do a profile.
Matthew smith: Yeah, that's right.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Max Ravech: So they also have account plans in Contender, which I don't know if we walked through that.
Max Ravech: An account plan is basically a client's whole journey from when they sign to when they inevitably go away and churn down the line. But that's where we keep track of their goals.
Max Ravech: It's where we keep track of activities that we've done on their behalf.
Max Ravech: any introductions, Any notes?
Max Ravech: And that also goes into our reporting, so when we send them a quarterly report, it pulls from that profile page on Contender.
Max Ravech: So we manually update that and, and set it up.
Matthew smith: Okay, and that's on Contender.
Max Ravech: That's all on Contender, yeah.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Max Ravech: But that's all… that's entirely manual. That never gets automatically… Nothing.
Matthew smith: Yeah, there were definitely… I mean, we found a couple loopholes to work around having API for Contender, but having access and having that API for Contender is going to be a huge help in just everything. Yeah, so…
Matthew smith: Boy, aye. Okay, cool. Make sure that's right.
Max Ravech: brand new campaigns, real client profile, LinkedIn.
Max Ravech: Yeah, after update contender is stale, you actually have to generate a…
Max Ravech: An email to send, so you have to…
Max Ravech: Before you select the B4B partners?
Max Ravech: It's like a… it's like an intro, like, this person is seeking these roles, he or she has done this in the past, like, you have to generate that… that email that goes to the top of their profile.
Matthew smith: Okay, so generic email.
Max Ravech: Which, again, is all manual.
Matthew smith: Email… Before the B2B4, B to 4.
Max Ravech: Yeah, before you pick the teams, yup.
Max Ravech: Send Whisper badges over 8 weeks. It's not always 8 weeks.
Max Ravech: But I get what you're saying.
Max Ravech: manually track which partners receive Profile.
Max Ravech: So we don't do that.
Matthew smith: Right here.
Max Ravech: Track which partners received the profile?
Matthew smith: Okay.
Max Ravech: In a spreadsheet. Yeah, that's on their contender profile in performance.
Max Ravech: It's like a performance tab.
Max Ravech: So we don't really do that.
Matthew smith: Okay, we'll take that out then.
Max Ravech: And we have a retool generator. We can go and select the time frame, past 6 months, and see all…
Max Ravech: We've sent them to. So we have tools to kind of get around that.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Max Ravech: Manually follow up with partners, yeah, sometimes.
Max Ravech: Track responses and inquiries, yeah, if we do that, report back, yeah, that's alright.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Max Ravech: The Chaos Zone, that's exactly what I would call it.
Max Ravech: You nailed it.
Max Ravech: It's controlled chaos.
Matthew smith: It's gotten you this far, so…
Max Ravech: Yeah, advisor conducts check every 3 months.
Max Ravech: Yeah.
Matthew smith: Yeah. Cool.
Max Ravech: It's already…
Matthew smith: Oh my goodness.
Max Ravech: 200, yup, two client ops on board.
Max Ravech: Good.
Max Ravech: I wouldn't call out Claire like that, she's actually better than the other two.
Max Ravech: And it's… her name's spelled wrong, not that that matters, C-L-A-R-E, but…
Matthew smith: I don't want her getting mad at me.
Max Ravech: Yeah, she's actually pretty good about it, and she doesn't… she has 2 clients, I think? She just started. Liv has 40, so she's kind of all over the place. David has the majority of them.
Max Ravech: But yeah, the Slack email thing's weird. I don't know where that came from, or why that stuck around.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Max Ravech: Check email for client tasks, yup.
Max Ravech: Yeah.
Matthew smith: Nice. Right. Okay.
Matthew smith: Do you have any questions so far? I know Kate… KB has some… some questions right now.
Max Ravech: You do? No, I'm good.
Matthew smith: Okay.
km Habib: I have some questions.
Max Ravech: Sure.
km Habib: Thanks, Miss. Thanks for making your time.
km Habib: Let me take the knot first.
km Habib: So, can you walk me through your typical day, like, what takes up most of the time, most of your time?
km Habib: In this, shot.
km Habib: If you can see us screen, it will be better.
Max Ravech: If I can share my screen.
Matthew smith: Yeah, it's not showing right now.
Max Ravech: Yeah.
Max Ravech: So… A lot… I have… there's, like, two parts to my job, and there's two parts to Lily's job.
Max Ravech: 60% of it is client service, 70% is client service, the other 30% is actually, like, building things and coming up with new ideas and new processes and new different things that we're trying to do. That 30% takes up a majority of my time, just because we're trying to build things.
Max Ravech: The client service part of it, The activities are not to…
Max Ravech: challenging. I mean, it's pretty tactical stuff. So…
Max Ravech: Depending on the client, depending on the task.
Max Ravech: What takes the most amount of time is probably a trending campaign.
Max Ravech: So it was on… it was on your sheet there. And the reason it takes so long is because I don't know who all of our B4B clients are, our Banff for Business clients. I don't know all of our search teams, I don't know all of our investors, I don't know what they do. So I have to do a lot of…
Max Ravech: checking of this client makes sense for this person, etc. So if I were to do a trending campaign in its totality.
Max Ravech: I have to do this, custom… I have to add the goal, why we're trending this person, so let's say it's for a new role. Subject, I have to come up with some creative subject line that makes sense, and then this is the draft, so Nella is looking for a new role.
Max Ravech: in XYZ. And then this is, like, a full paragraph.
Max Ravech: And then these are the templates that we create for her. These get stored on her Contender profile, but depending, again, on what we're trending her for and why, we have to go through and fix these up a little bit.
Max Ravech: And then, this is where we choose all of the teams that we want to center to.
Max Ravech: And because there's…
Max Ravech: 300 of them, and our filters don't really work too well. They're very generalized, and a lot of people don't fill them out.
Max Ravech: I kind of have to search my own stuff, so, like, CFO world.
Max Ravech: you know, you have to kind of read through these. Does this team make sense?
Max Ravech: And then you pick about 15 to 20 teams for each campaign, generally.
Max Ravech: And then you go into scheduling…
Max Ravech: You pick the start date, which can be today.
Max Ravech: We do custom spread, usually select the number of weeks, it goes over, those 20 teams get sent, generate it, and it does this. So all in all, that… that is, like, the longest task. It probably takes 20 to 30 minutes, realistically.
km Habib: Damn.
Max Ravech: Any questions there?
km Habib: Great, great, got that. So, if I could magically give you 10 hours back this week, which one talks would you eliminate concretely?
Max Ravech: I think it would be…
Max Ravech: If I could eliminate one task, is that… that was the question? Just one thing?
km Habib: Yes.
Max Ravech: 10 hours of work back.
Max Ravech: I do a lot of these.
km Habib: Trending.
Max Ravech: trending campaigns.
km Habib: Okay.
Max Ravech: And reports. So I send a lot of reports to our clients. On a quarterly basis, they all get a quarterly report. It has all the introductions that they've had in the past quarter, any events they've been invited to, it has their goals.
Max Ravech: That…
Max Ravech: that document is riddled with bad data, and I don't trust anything that it generates, so I need to spend probably
Max Ravech: 5 to 10 minutes on each report before I send it out, and that takes forever, because you have to go through Notion, you have to go through HubSpot emails, Contender.
Max Ravech: cross-reference it. I can show you what that looks like, but that takes a very long time, also.
km Habib: Obviously, you finally understand that. Okay, that's great. Now the next question is, what breaks the most often? Like, what makes you go, oh crap, not against moment, like, if you face that?
Max Ravech: what breaks?
Max Ravech: I think our infrastructure has gotten a lot better in the past year. Stuff doesn't break too often. We have a HubSpot to Notion sync that
Max Ravech: Can break, or maybe not break's the right word, but if you do something wrong, it will mess up.
Max Ravech: A lot of…
km Habib: true, mostly.
km Habib: Okay, so mostly fine.
km Habib: If I consider it.
km Habib: Okay, so you also, do the onboarding, onboarding, right?
km Habib: Yeah, so can you screen share and walk me through the last client you onboarded? Basically, I want to see the actual process that will help me.
Max Ravech: Sure.
km Habib: Nosta.
Max Ravech: See, if we have any new ones, maybe we do.
Max Ravech: So again, Arthur sends them all. We can take… we can do this client. I already set him up, but it's fine.
Max Ravech: Alright, so Chris Quay came in, Arthur sent me the contract with all of the details.
Max Ravech: It has billing information, how he's gonna pay, and
Max Ravech: you know, this stuff down here, his address. This is what I was talking about, of, like, me not knowing who Chris Quay is, like, I looked him up, and I was like…
Max Ravech: Sorry. Anything?
Max Ravech: Is there a question? No? Good. So this is, like, the thing where,
Max Ravech: I have to email David and be like, is this Chris? Because I have no idea.
Max Ravech: So that takes a little bit of extra work.
Max Ravech: So I have to go into HubSpot, I have to go to his… profile…
Max Ravech: I do some reviewing on how they've talked to each other in the past, why he's coming in to work with us, all that good stuff, just for some background.
Max Ravech: I'll add his LinkedIn.
Max Ravech: Change him to current private advisor, because that's what he is after he signs his contract. David's the advisor. He's in transition services.
Max Ravech: Contract start date is when we receive this.
Max Ravech: Billing terms… billing terms are all… they're mostly the same. 99% of the time, they're all the same. The weird 1% we deal with.
Max Ravech: Add next billing date, payment method, onboarding, all of that good stuff is in the contract.
Max Ravech: So again, once I… once I change him from nothing to Tier 1 executive client.
Max Ravech: His Notion page will generate itself.
Max Ravech: So all I have to do, go to Client Services Home, Go into Exec Clients.
Max Ravech: just type in Chris, and he'll pop up.
Max Ravech: And then the only thing that we do here is we copy and paste this HubSpot link.
Max Ravech: I think there's some… there's a reason why we do that, I don't know why, and we do Contender. Like, all these people have unique Contender IDs, you'll find that out when you get access to it, but they all link to different things, and they're needed for tracking.
Max Ravech: And then I just make… this is like a little button I just select, it makes them a client, and it gives us these… these databases.
Max Ravech: So all of these… these are all separate databases that we keep track of?
Max Ravech: And whenever you tag a client, it just shows up on their page.
Max Ravech: So this is… these are all of our manual trackers down here.
Max Ravech: So whenever a client sends us a new executive search, we go in, We lost, we lost.
Max Ravech: The other guy, I think.
Max Ravech: Let me hopped back in.
Max Ravech: Who's here.
Matthew smith: June.
Matthew smith: Oh boy, that's fine.
Max Ravech: No, Mick, you've gone.
Matthew smith: Yeah, that's fine.
Max Ravech: So, these are all the manual trackers that we have. So, a client will send us a search or a job that they were called for.
Max Ravech: over email, And what happens is we have a Zap set up.
Max Ravech: So that we can just forward that email to an active searches email distro, and it goes in here, and it fills out all of these sections.
Max Ravech: All these columns get sent, get filled out.
Max Ravech: But the manual part of this is having to add our client's name so that it tags back to their Notion page.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Matthew smith: Nice.
Max Ravech: I kind of got away from the onboarding stuff, but… and then you go to Contender, and you add their
Max Ravech: exec client.
Max Ravech: Things.
Max Ravech: Change them to an exec client, add their onboarding date when that happens, their kickoff date.
Max Ravech: This is the account plan thing I was talking about.
Matthew smith: Okay. You wanna walk us through that?
Matthew smith: Got it.
Matthew smith: Count plan.
Matthew smith: Start warning, okay, I see what I see.
Matthew smith: Hello?
Max Ravech: Well, for some people.
Matthew smith: Lost you for a second.
Max Ravech: Don't know what's going on here… There we go.
Max Ravech: So these are all the onboarding steps that we have to take care of. This is it, this is everything.
Matthew smith: Okay, let me see.
Max Ravech: So as you go through this.
Max Ravech: You just check off all these boxes.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Matthew smith: Yes.
Max Ravech: And you'll see that, like, I… I… we already did this stuff. Like, I'm…
Max Ravech: I'm here with him. But it doesn't affect anything if I go do it now, even though he kicked off last week.
Max Ravech: I've gotten so used to kicking off clients that I don't need to keep track of it this way.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Matthew smith: And so, if you keep… if you knock all those out, does… that doesn't go anywhere? Or is that just on container for yourself?
Max Ravech: It doesn't do… it doesn't do anything.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Max Ravech: So a lot of the times, I'll come in here two weeks later, I'll just mark it complete, like, we kicked him off, and off he goes. But it doesn't notify anybody, it doesn't launch any new activities, it doesn't do anything.
Max Ravech: And then this part's all manual.
Max Ravech: So, each client has two to three goals. They usually have an active job-seeking goal, a board-seeking goal, and a network-building goal.
Max Ravech: So you just have to go and add JobSeeker, you select the program, job seeker, end date is usually 6 months out for a job seeker. In progress, high.
Max Ravech: And then what you can do is you can attach these to a goal, a specific goal, if it makes sense.
Matthew smith: Nice, okay.
Max Ravech: So you can see which…
Max Ravech: Peer executives, after connecting activities, you can go peer executives, how many search firm intros, investor, corporate, and you can add notes.
Max Ravech: People don't look at this as often as they should, in my opinion, just because it's a little messy. Sometimes it's out of date.
Max Ravech: But this is an account plan.
Max Ravech: And then these get tagged into their quarterly reports, all of these goals, they get automatically copied and pasted.
Matthew smith: And then, do you have any, like, documentation for any of this, or how do you train?
Matthew smith: People, when they… when they first sign on with you guys.
Max Ravech: We do, yeah, yeah, we do. I don't have, like, looms.
Max Ravech: But I have a… Account plans here. It'll walk you through everything, step by step.
Matthew smith: There he is.
Matthew smith: Lawyers, right?
Max Ravech: lost you.
Matthew smith: Yeah.
Max Ravech: Yeah, but this is a… this is how we onboard people.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Matthew smith: Yeah, that's, that's definitely useful, so…
Max Ravech: Probably take a…
Matthew smith: If you want to send that over, that would be amazing.
Max Ravech: Yeah, you guys can click through all of these. I mean, this is everything step-by-step in what we do.
Matthew smith: Nice, okay.
Matthew smith: Cool, cool, cool, cool.
Max Ravech: Do you have access to this Notion doc?
Matthew smith: You're back, yeah.
Matthew smith: No. Nothing yet. That's why we're going through this again, so we need to get access to that. Once we have access to that, then it's probably…
Matthew smith: We'll probably answer a lot of our own questions.
Max Ravech: Yeah, there's a shit ton of, of processes and weird flyer thoughts that people had. You just have to kind of click through. But this is our home base, this client service is home. Everything that I do is here.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Km Habib: So, can you show me your inbox right now, like, what does a typical tax email from Debit, debit look like?
Max Ravech: Task email, yeah, sure. So, it's usually the… Client's… client's name.
Max Ravech: And… That's it. So, I can find one here quickly.
Max Ravech: So, a sheet is a client that we have.
Max Ravech: His name is Ashit Mehta, so if you were brand new to Banff, you would have no idea who this guy is. Like, this is just how familiar we are with our client base. But a to-do, it's usually a question, sometimes it's a question to everybody at Banff.
Max Ravech: Do we know anybody at this company? Client ops, can you P2P, which is peer-to-peer on Contender?
Max Ravech: Sheet to these two people.
Max Ravech: Here's the context for the intros.
Max Ravech: And then, this is David Bomer.
Max Ravech: He'll send me his bio in LinkedIn. I don't know what that means or what that's for, but…
Max Ravech: I don't… I don't really care. He'll figure that out.
Max Ravech: So that's… that's that. This is a very typical task email.
Km Habib: Alright, so basically, Liv and Claire, communicate differently than David, right?
Max Ravech: Liv and Claire, yeah, sure. So…
Km Habib: Can you show me your Slack talks versus an email talks? I saw the email talks, can you show me any Slack talks?
Km Habib: Living for your province.
Max Ravech: Yeah. So these are all of Liv's clients.
Max Ravech: And what Liv does.
Max Ravech: Which is not sustainable, because I'm not looking through 200 Slack channels when she has that many clients. So, she sets up one for each client.
Max Ravech: And… You're basically just kinda, like…
Max Ravech: rant. Like, there's a good thing and a bad thing to this, is that we're, like, inside Liv's brain, so we never miss anything, but it's more like stream of consciousness, like…
Max Ravech: I don't know.
Km Habib: Okay.
Max Ravech: If we haven't already, like, trend… send a trending campaign to these teams.
Max Ravech: Or… You can see I'm very active in these.
Matthew smith: Yeah.
Max Ravech: But everyone, every client's a little bit different.
Max Ravech: These are, like, weird ad hoc tasks.
Km Habib: Oh, great.
Km Habib: Intro, like, do an intro request, narrative edits.
Max Ravech: I don't know, again, every question… er, everyone's a little bit different.
Km Habib: Yeah, got it.
Max Ravech: Peer-to-peer.
Km Habib: The next question is when, 5 zoom transcript dumped into ocean at the same time? Basically, how do you figure out which one belongs to whom?
Max Ravech: each claim.
Max Ravech: Yeah.
Max Ravech: That's a good question.
Max Ravech: So we have… We have a client…
Max Ravech: data validation that our old CTO set up when she was here. Basically, what it does is it filters for empty columns, and it pulls everything into this doc.
Max Ravech: So, these are, again, all linked to different databases.
Max Ravech: They're all named… like, these meetings are usually all named appropriately.
Max Ravech: like, this was a client call that I had today, so I would tag it to her profile.
Max Ravech: this, I don't know who it is.
Max Ravech: But it's Tim Powell, like, you click into it and you see that it's Tim Powell.
Max Ravech: Who's not a client, by the way, which makes this even more confusing.
Max Ravech: Your guys' meeting… Huh?
Matthew smith: I said, who's Tim, then?
Max Ravech: So that's like a… that would be a sales call. That's like a sales channel. So Tim Powell may sign a contract in 3 months, and I'll have to go and find Tim Powell's sales calls, and tag them.
Matthew smith: You guys don't tag that as well? You guys don't tag, like, potential clients?
Max Ravech: No, they don't, they don't get these pages.
Max Ravech: These are only clients?
Km Habib: Okay.
Km Habib: Go ahead.
Matthew smith: And you keep, you keep everything, like, the CRM HubSpot, like, potential clients, we've had a sales call with this guy, and it's moved on to a client.
Matthew smith: Right, HubSpot.
Max Ravech: I don't do that.
Max Ravech: No, I don't know if they do that either, honestly.
Max Ravech: No, my job starts when I get the contract.
Max Ravech: Pretty much.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Km Habib: So, suppose here is this interview, David emails you four tasks, and Lib…
Km Habib: Selects you two texts, and there is a Zoom transcription with, Claire mentioning one tux. So basically, how do you handle that?
Max Ravech: Okay, so David emails a task, Liv slacks me a task, and what was the third part of that?
Km Habib: And there's a Zoom transcription with Claire mentioning one tax.
Max Ravech: Huh.
Km Habib: How do you handle that?
Max Ravech: So I have a task list. Whenever, like, I become aware of a task in whatever form, I have a task list that I keep updated.
Max Ravech: These are all my in-progress tasks that I'm working on. So it's kind of like stream of conscious, like, David sends me a task, I respond and say, okay, got it. Liv slacks me, okay, got it, I'll handle this. Claire, whatever, does something, sends me a task. I'll just put in the task here, I'll add a date, and…
Max Ravech: I'll just keep looking at these. I usually start here during my day. Like, I'll just check out what I have to do.
Km Habib: Okay.
Km Habib: It's a manual searching, right. So, basically, after the first two months, like, kickoff narratives and tendings, I think you do this client-side.
Km Habib: Basically narrative, sites, drafting, LinkedIn profile building.
Km Habib: Etcetera.
Max Ravech: Is there an objective?
Km Habib: No, I mean, you do this as the client… as you work in the client side.
Km Habib: Yeah.
Max Ravech: do all that. Yeah.
Km Habib: So, so sometimes things get more, in ad hoc, right? So, like, what is the most time-consuming ad hoc request you see?
Max Ravech: So it…
Max Ravech: If we feel like we're not providing value to a client, we'll do some crazy stuff. Like, we'll kind of…
Max Ravech: pull value from anywhere we can. I think the most time-consuming one is something we call target company mapping.
Max Ravech: We're basically… we take…
Max Ravech: I can show you what one looks like. And this doesn't happen very often, right? This is kind of like a one-off, but it does take forever.
Max Ravech: So we take a client's goals, their companies that they'd like to work at, and basically we go and find
Max Ravech: 30 to 40 companies that we think that they should work at. Like, it's interesting companies for them.
Max Ravech: That… we use ChatGPT to find those companies, we use our own network to find those companies, we use HubSpot, Contender people pages to find potential connections.
Max Ravech: And what that… What that deliverable looks like.
Max Ravech: It's something.
Matthew smith: I use…
Matthew smith: Sorry, I didn't mean to cut you off. But is that similar to, like, a training campaign? It seems like it kind of does the same thing, right?
Matthew smith: Hormone.
Max Ravech: Yeah, no, you're… you're right. That…
Max Ravech: This is more direct company outreach. Those are search firms and investors, so that's more broader conversations.
Max Ravech: But, I mean, this would be literally, like, a Nike Peloton, and then he goes in, the client goes in and says, I'm interested in this company, I'm not interested in this company, is there any action? Like, we'll share your profile. So this is a ton of coordination between all of our systems and the client, and it takes forever.
Max Ravech: There are ways to make this easier, but it's… for now, it's just really hard.
Km Habib: So, basically, it's unstructured way you handle this.
Matthew smith: At a previous trip, right?
Max Ravech: We've tried to structure it, it's just such a big, big thing that it's… it's difficult. But again, this is rare. I maybe do two of these, three of these a month.
Km Habib: Oh, got it. So, the next question is, when you do P2P in true? So basically, can you walk me through it, like, how do you find both profile, draft the email, and track it?
Max Ravech: Sure, yeah.
Max Ravech: Okay, so you go here. This is our peer-to-peer page.
Max Ravech: To submit a new match, basically. So let's say, whatever, a new client signs, like Chris Quay.
Max Ravech: The guy I showed you.
Max Ravech: If you find his profile, go to continue.
Max Ravech: These are all of the people that we could introduce to Chris.
Km Habib: Okay.
Max Ravech: the qualifying statement is, because I've been here for so long, I know who our clients are enough to not have to go to their individual client pages or ask anybody else. Like, I can do this myself.
Max Ravech: someone like Lily, when she first started, or any new client ops person, it would take them a long, long time to do this.
Max Ravech: So, I know that Chris is in real estate, and he's in automobiles, so, like, I have an idea already of who I could do. I don't know, like, Monica works for a big real estate firm.
Max Ravech: So you go and you select it,
Max Ravech: This is where we do our approval, so every peer-to-peer has to get approved, unless an advisor says, no, it's already approved, just go do it. But everything is set up as ready for review, so this will go to Olivia, or Liv, for approval. She'll get an email
Max Ravech: She will have to wait for her to approve it. We have to give a reason for the match, so it'd be, like, real estate.
Max Ravech: conversation, I don't know.
Max Ravech: You submit it, And then it goes to Liv for… Approval?
Max Ravech: After it gets approved… Huh.
Max Ravech: It goes to green.
Max Ravech: Which basically means that we have the go-ahead to create an email.
Matthew smith: Nope.
Matthew smith: There's tons of minimal work here.
Km Habib: And this down.
Max Ravech: And you can schedule it out, so if they have a full calendar already, you can go and.
Km Habib: et cetera.
Max Ravech: for mid-December, or something like that, schedule it.
Max Ravech: But again, like, you have to add more context here, because these people will email you back and be like, what the F, why are you emailing? Like, I don't want to meet this person, even though we know why they should be meeting. So you have to curate some context in this intro email.
Matthew smith: Truthfully, what's causing you guys the biggest headache, what it seems like, is not having… Contender automated.
Max Ravech: Yeah, that's… that's been a problem.
Matthew smith: So, if you were to just go in and automate this, a lot of your headaches would be cleared.
Max Ravech: Yeah, and the reason we struggle with automation is because
Max Ravech: it's, like, counterintuitive for this business to be automated, just because of how personal it is. So if we were to automatically generate an intro email, there's a chance it sounds like BS, they call us on it, and it's like, yikes. Like, we've tried to automatically introduce people before.
Max Ravech: It rarely works, just because they look for us to
Max Ravech: you know, know them better than themselves in a weird way. So, yes, I mean, if Contender was automated and we had all the information we needed to make an intro, it would be awesome, but we've hit roadblocks before.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Km Habib: So, what five automation do you, think that can be, revolutionary in your task?
Km Habib: If you rank them 1 to 5.
Max Ravech: I see no reason for peer-to-peers to be automated.
Max Ravech: You would have to do a lot of legwork, you would have to reach out to Satnam and say, hey, Satnam, I'm gonna introduce you to these 8 people over the next 8 months, and give you all the context, so that when you get the email, you don't even think about it.
Max Ravech: Like, that's… that is a lot of legwork, but an easy form of automation.
Max Ravech: Trending campaigns can't be automated. They can, I'm sure there's some automation, but just the level, and how many people are involved, and the potential backfire of something going wrong, that would be an issue.
Max Ravech: I think kickoff and onboarding, we could automate a lot of it. We're just…
Max Ravech: The thing that we… it's one very, very small thing that we can't seem to figure out, and that is the actually of tagging a client's Notion page to all of these activities. Like, we can't get this to automate. Everything else is,
Max Ravech: But these…
Max Ravech: this column here, this client thing, we can't automate it. I don't know why. We can't figure it out.
Km Habib: Okay.
Max Ravech: But everything else gets filled in, you know? That's the weird part.
Max Ravech: So that would save me, I don't know, 5-6 hours a week going through.
Km Habib: Okay… That's got it.
Km Habib: Now, when you talk about onboarding. So, basically, after onboarding, you send the welcome email with kickoff scheduler, right?
Max Ravech: Yes.
Km Habib: So, does this work smoothly, or do client ghost sometimes?
Max Ravech: Oh, good call out.
Max Ravech: They will ghost for a week, and then we follow up, and we usually get them, at the very least, on the second email.
Km Habib: Majority don't. Majority get back pretty quickly.
Max Ravech: They just paid us a lot of money, so I would hope they… Engagement.
Matthew smith: Hopefully intensive.
Max Ravech: Nope.
Matthew smith: Okay, cool.
Km Habib: And if I ask you, TSQ, so Hawaiian TSQ sends you the sign of… signed contract PDF? So, basically, do you see any information missing, that you have to hunt for?
Max Ravech: Sometimes. Not really. No.
Max Ravech: We usually have everything we need.
Matthew smith: Come on.
Km Habib: That's fine.
Km Habib: Okay.
Km Habib: That's it, that's all questions I have to ask you.
Matthew smith: Cool.
Matthew smith: Nice.
Matthew smith: So…
Km Habib: We got, we went through everything.
Matthew smith: We kind of got… we make sure we are following all the steps, everything's approved. Do you have any questions for us?
Max Ravech: I don't, no, no. Okay. But again, like, everything that I do is… is here. This is it.
Max Ravech: there's more to it, but, like, if you guys look through this document, you'll figure out what I do, pretty much.
Matthew smith: Nice. Okay.
Km Habib: So, there is one platform for all the Banff executives, or separately maintain each other. I mean, separately maintains notions, like other platforms also.
Km Habib: Do you handles all in one platform?
Max Ravech: Handle all of what in one platform? Client tasks?
Km Habib: clientex, plus, processing onboarding to, manage everything. Do you have, do you have any other, platform that you do separately in your separate own domain or environment?
Km Habib: Or work in one place.
Km Habib: centralized.
Max Ravech: It's not one plate, yeah, so it's… HubSpot, Notion, Contender, Retool.
Max Ravech: I use chat.
Km Habib: No.
Max Ravech: But not for… Managing clients, it's more for, like, Creative stuff.
Km Habib: Like, in Notion, one place you all handle all of this, or do you have any particular domain for individuals?
Km Habib: like,
Km Habib: if you handle… if you have your own Notion space that you handle some of your… some of your tasks, or all you do in one Notion account, if I say that.
Max Ravech: I don't have my own Notion, no.
Km Habib: Now, I'm in, you have your own database.
Matthew smith: where everything's kind of falling to. Is that right, Kim?
Km Habib: Yep, yep, yep.
Max Ravech: My own database. I'm sorry, I'm just not…
Km Habib: So basically, all of your executives work in one Notion account, and I can see, or I can get all these data from this one account. This is what I mean?
Max Ravech: Oh, yeah.
Max Ravech: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Everybody works in here. Yep.
Km Habib: Oh, that's great.
Km Habib: So, would you need to look for another platform, or in other accounts. This is the one account that you got all the information. Basically, the structural information.
Max Ravech: This is it, yeah, everybody's here. Yep.
Matthew smith: Okay, great.
Km Habib: Contact.
Matthew smith: Solid. So, I guess the main objectives would be kickoff.
Matthew smith: The kickoff, onboarding, and then follow-up, along with client meeting notes.
Matthew smith: Probably our main automations. Sound about right?
Max Ravech: Got this on right. Yeah, client onboarding…
Max Ravech: And then, anything that we can automate in those tasks that we get from advisors, we can look at, but that would be awesome, yeah.
Matthew smith: Awesome.
Max Ravech: That's all it is.
Matthew smith: Sounds good, Maxwell, I appreciate your time.
Matthew smith: We'll be in contact with anything, any updates, of course.
Max Ravech: Sweet. I'm here. Any questions, let me know.
Km Habib: Let's get it. Cheers, man. Thanks, guys.
Matthew smith: Thanks, Iran.